thepayerplayer.com 2011-12-08

# Privacy Policy | Lucid Meetings

Lucid Meetings (Service) is a product of Second Rise, LLC.

Second Rise, LLC is committed to protect the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy outlines what information we collect and how we may use it on www.lucidmeetings.com, help.lucidmeetings.com, and meet.lucidmeetings.com.

Maintaining the privacy of your information is of paramount importance to us as it helps foster confidence, goodwill and stronger relationships with you, our customers. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please feel free contact us at support at secondrise dot com.

When you register with Lucid Meetings, we need to ask for information such as your name, company name, email address.

Second Rise uses the collected information for the following general purposes: to create your account, provide you with email communications in regards to our service, to send you newsletters, service improvement, and research.

This privacy policy does not cover any personal or sensitive information collected within the application. Please refer to the Terms of Service for our policy regarding information within the application.

Second Rise will not make any of the collected information available to anyone. We will never sell, rent, exchange or share your personal information with third parties other than as disclosed within this privacy policy. We reserve the right to transfer information about you if Second Rise or Lucid Meetings is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Second Rise will notify you before information you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Second Rise will need to share the collected information in order to respond to investigation, court orders, legal process, or to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Second Rise’s Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

Second Rise reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site or Service.

### Newsletters

As part of the service that we offer you will receive our monthly newsletter. We will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters you may unsubscribe by following the unsubscribe link located within each email communication.

### Emails

Second Rise will send out emails for billing purposes, service notifications, as well as those issued by the Service, such as meeting invitations.

### Cookies

Second Rise uses a technology called "cookies" to store session information. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Second Rise may set and access Second Rise or Lucid Meetings cookies on your computer, cookies are required to use the Lucid Meetings service. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

### Third Party Cookies

The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. These third parties use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

### Third Party Services

Second Rise uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Lucid Meetings. Although Second Rise owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Lucid Meetings application, you retain all rights to your data.

### Customer Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

### Blog

If you use the blog on this web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these blogs, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these blogs.

### Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at support at secondrise dot com.

### Updates to the Privacy Policy

Second Rise may periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Lucid Meetings account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

If you have any question about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support at secondrise dot com.

Second Rise may be contacted at the following address:

Second Rise, LLC  
3551 SW Vermont St  
Portland OR 97219  
USA
